{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Chain Link Fence Installers","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40052/":{"taskOID":40052,"originalTaskOID":40052,"setID":375,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5554,"questionDisplayText":"Nature of Project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the nature of this project?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":200204,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Replace existing fence","answerDisplayText":"Replace existing fence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200206,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Repair existing fence","answerDisplayText":"Repair existing fence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200205,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Install a new fence ","answerDisplayText":"Install a new fence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":827,"questionDisplayText":"Fence Height","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the height of the fence you want to have installed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3552,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 4 feet","answerDisplayText":"Less than 4 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":486,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"4-6 feet","answerDisplayText":"4-6 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":546,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"6-8 feet","answerDisplayText":"6-8 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2859,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Greater than 8 feet","answerDisplayText":"Greater than 8 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":500140,"questionDisplayText":"Length of Fence","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Approximately, how many linear feet of fencing do you need? ","shortQuestionText":"Approximately, how many linear feet of fencing do you need? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":200201,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 100 feet","answerDisplayText":"Less than 100 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200202,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"100 - 200 feet","answerDisplayText":"100 - 200 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200203,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"201 - 300 feet","answerDisplayText":"201 - 300 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200200,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Over 300 feet","answerDisplayText":"Over 300 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5355,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Gate","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which type of gate would you like? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5735,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Single walk gate","answerDisplayText":"Single walk gate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1775,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Custom walk gate","answerDisplayText":"Custom walk gate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3733,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Manual driveway gate","answerDisplayText":"Manual driveway gate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":896,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Automatic driveway gate","answerDisplayText":"Automatic driveway gate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5554,"questionDisplayText":"Nature of Project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the nature of this project?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":200204,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Replace existing fence","answerDisplayText":"Replace existing fence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200206,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Repair existing fence","answerDisplayText":"Repair existing fence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200205,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Install a new fence ","answerDisplayText":"Install a new fence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":200204,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Replace existing fence","answerDisplayText":"Replace existing fence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200206,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Repair existing fence","answerDisplayText":"Repair existing fence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200205,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Install a new fence ","answerDisplayText":"Install a new fence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":827,"questionDisplayText":"Fence Height","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the height of the fence you want to have installed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3552,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 4 feet","answerDisplayText":"Less than 4 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":486,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"4-6 feet","answerDisplayText":"4-6 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":546,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"6-8 feet","answerDisplayText":"6-8 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2859,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Greater than 8 feet","answerDisplayText":"Greater than 8 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3552,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 4 feet","answerDisplayText":"Less than 4 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":486,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"4-6 feet","answerDisplayText":"4-6 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":546,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"6-8 feet","answerDisplayText":"6-8 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2859,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Greater than 8 feet","answerDisplayText":"Greater than 8 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":500140,"questionDisplayText":"Length of Fence","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Approximately, how many linear feet of fencing do you need? ","shortQuestionText":"Approximately, how many linear feet of fencing do you need? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":200201,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 100 feet","answerDisplayText":"Less than 100 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200202,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"100 - 200 feet","answerDisplayText":"100 - 200 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200203,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"201 - 300 feet","answerDisplayText":"201 - 300 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200200,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Over 300 feet","answerDisplayText":"Over 300 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":200201,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 100 feet","answerDisplayText":"Less than 100 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200202,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"100 - 200 feet","answerDisplayText":"100 - 200 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200203,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"201 - 300 feet","answerDisplayText":"201 - 300 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200200,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Over 300 feet","answerDisplayText":"Over 300 feet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5355,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Gate","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which type of gate would you like? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5735,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Single walk gate","answerDisplayText":"Single walk gate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1775,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Custom walk gate","answerDisplayText":"Custom walk gate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3733,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Manual driveway gate","answerDisplayText":"Manual driveway gate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":896,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Automatic driveway gate","answerDisplayText":"Automatic driveway gate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5735,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Single walk gate","answerDisplayText":"Single walk gate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1775,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Custom walk gate","answerDisplayText":"Custom walk gate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3733,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Manual driveway gate","answerDisplayText":"Manual driveway gate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":896,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Automatic driveway gate","answerDisplayText":"Automatic driveway gate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40052/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40052,"taskName":"Chain Link Fence - Install","taskDescription":"Install a Chain Link Fence","xmTaskDescriptor":"Chain Link Fence Installers","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":373,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"chain link fence fencing yard","textMessagingName":"Inst Chain Fence","rolloverLongDesc":"Very sturdy, long-lasting fence. Usually gray in color from the galvanizing process that delays rusting. Sometimes comes in a colorful plastic-coated versions.  Sometimes has plastic strips woven into the mesh to create more privacy.","rolloverShortDesc":"Metal fencing made from woven heavy wires.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install a Chain Link Fence.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Chain Link Fence Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Replace a Chain Fence","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":30,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Chain Link Fence Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Chain Link Fence - Install","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Chain Link Fence Project","urlName":"Chain-Link-Fence-Install","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Chain Link Fence Installers - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Costs \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"chain,link,fence,fencing,yard","emcCategoryOid":-12030,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":375,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false}}